# Abhilasha B R

# Software Engineer

- abhibhagya4542@gmail.com
  - +91 7899210332
- 560032
- iii 01/05/1996 ♣ Female **◎** Single

- India
- in https://linkedin.com/in/abhilasha-br-1bbba824a
- https://github.com/AbhilashaAbhiBR
- https://gitlab.com/abhilashabr\_br\_96

#### **Profile**

Enthusiastic and reliable React Developer with a strong knowledge of Javascript, Reactis, NodeJs, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Vuejs and basic knowledge of Core Java and Spring boot. 2.4 years of IT industry experience as a part of computer program development team.

#### Skills

JavaScript, ReactJs, Redux, Vuejs, HTML, CSS/SCSS, GIT, Core Java, Data Structures, Python, Azure Devops, Oracle, Springboot, NodeJs (API Communications), JSON

## **Projects**

#### **IRIS**

- Tools
- Visual Studio Code
- Description
  - One platform for all advisory, contact centers and back-offices employees to handle every customer demand with ease. Iris can be regarded as the backbone to which all customer data and processes are linked.

# Mlikpot

- Description
  - This is a web and mobile application for online milk products retail which includes wallet, subscription, etc.

# **Professional Experience**

#### **Software Engineer, HCL Tech**

05/2022 - 08/2023 | Bangalore, India

- Use React with NodeJs, Lit-HTML technologies to develop web applications and add functionalities to existing applications.
- Experience in developing web applications with Reactjs, Redux.
- Conduct user requirements analysis to design and program applications and deliver support for system enhancement.
- Worked in assisted channel tribe.
- API Integration
- Play a pivotal role as a part of agile scrum team

#### **Software Engineer Trainee,**

Anavadya Softech Private Limited 07/2021 - 03/2022 | Bangalore, India

- Use Vueis and Nodeis technologies to develop web applications and add functionalities to existing applications.
- Experience in developing web applications with
- Conduct user requirements analysis to design and program applications and deliver support for system enhancement.
- Giving application demos to the customer.
- Developed highly interactive and customized UIs using Vuejs, Javacript, HTML, CSS to improve the functionality of web applications.
- Play a pivotal role as a part of agile scrum team accountable, developing new applications using Fornt end Javascipt frameworks.

#### Languages

English Kannada Hindi Telugu

# **Education**

### **Master of Computer Application,**

Maharani's Science College for Women 2017 - 2020 | Bangalore, India

# **Bachelor of Computer Application,**

Sri Aurobindo First Grade College For Women 2014 - 2017 | Bangalore, India

#### INTERMEDIAT,

Sri Aurobindo Composite PU College For Women 2012 - 2014 | Bangalore, India

- In this project mainly focusing on the UI design i.e Customer Registration, Dashboard, Functionalities like Login mobile OTP, Subcribe or skip/unskip milk subscription and also worked on API integration for the same app.
- Also worked fixing the bugs raised by the testing teams

# **Buy O Property**

- Description
  - This is a web application for direct property purchase and selling and Serenity Hostels.
  - In this project mainly focusing on the UI design i.e Agent registration, Add property in admin protal and also worked on API integration for the same app.
  - Also worked fixing the bugs raised by the testing teams.

# Certificates

• Python Full stack Developer Course

**High School,** *T S Subbabba Sarvajanika High School* 2009 – 2012 | Mandya, India

### **Interests**

Drawing, Painting, Learning new technologies